fabrily.com 2016-05-28

# Fabrily

###  **1\. INTRODUCTION**

1.1 Our Privacy Policy is designed to ensure that the personal data you provide to us is processed with due care and attention. The owner of Fabrily.com (the “Website”) is Fabrily Ltd (“We” or “Us”) are committed to our users’ privacy.

1.2 This policy (together with our Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting the Website you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

1.3 We collect, store, use and protect your personal information in a transparent way in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1988 (the “Act”), the data controller is Fabrily Ltd of Office 34, 67-68 Hatton Garden, London EC1N 8JY, United Kingdom. Fabrily is registered with the ICO under registration number [ ].

1.4 If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, then please do not use the Website.

###  **2\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

2.1 We may collect the following data:

(a) information about you including but not limited to your name and contact details which you provided while filling out our electronic forms on the Website or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. Our payment services provider may collect, process and store your payment details. The privacy policy of our payment services provider applies in relation to the collection and processing of such data. We will not receive your payment details;

(b) information provided at the time of registering to use the Website, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services;

(c) information about you from the requests and other messages you submit to the Website and the e-mails or letters you send to us;

(d) information about your visit to the Website including but not limited to weblogs, traffic and location data or any other communication information;

(e) information from surveys conducted by the Website from time to time. However, you are not obliged to respond to them; and

(f) details of transactions you carry out through the Website and of the fulfillment of your orders.

2.2 The personal data collected by us may be used:

(a) to meet any request you make on the Website and deliver the services you demand;

(b) to adhere to any contractual Agreements entered into by the Website;

(c) to contact you where it is necessary concerning the services you demand;

(d) to keep you informed of the Website services and news;

(e) to improve and develop our service by monitoring website usage;

(f) to notify you about changes to our services; and

(g) for survey purposes.

###  **3\. IP ADDRESSES**

3.1 We may collect, store and use information about your computer, mobile device or other item of hardware through which you access the Website including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

###  **4\. INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**

4.1 We share your personal information with our staff, business partners, suppliers and contractors only to the extent and for the purpose for which it was supplied (for the avoidance of doubt this may include, but is not limited to, the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you).

4.2 We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006. We may also release information relating to you if we are required to do so by legal process or in response to a subpoena, court order or other legitimate request by an authority.

4.3 We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

(a) in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;

(b) if Fabrily Ltd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;

(c) in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Fabrily Ltd, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction;

(d) to allow Campaign Creators to contact you about current, previous or future Campaigns.

4.4 We may transfer or sell your personal information to a third party in the context of an acquisition of substantially the entire issued share capital of Fabrily or the sale of the business and assets of Fabrily. You irrevocably authorise us to transfer or sell your personal information in such circumstances and irrevocably consent to such a transfer or sale.

4.5 Prior to transferring or selling your personal information, we would seek assurances hat the transferee complies with UK laws in respect of the handling and processing of your personal data or laws with equivalent protections to those in the UK.

4.6 We do not disclose the data you provided to us to any other third parties unless you have specifically consented to it or for the purposes of complying with a legal or regulatory requirement. We may use data or allow relevant third parties to market to you if you have agreed to this option.

4.7 We may in our sole and absolute discretion provide a person who has claimed that any Products infringe their intellectual property rights with some or all of the below information to assist them with evaluating their losses, damages and any claim they may have against a campaign creator. Please note that we are under no obligation to disclose this information and do so solely in our discretion in a manner and at a time that we believe is appropriate. We would not generally disclose financial information relating to any campaign without the campaign creator’s consent and/or when we consider it necessary for the dispute to be resolved:

(a) name and contact details of the campaign creator;

(b) date of creation of the campaign;

(c) number of orders made in relation to the campaign and/or number of Products sold; and

(d) sums received by the campaign creator after deduction of our fees and charges.

###  **5\. DATA SAFEKEEPING**

5.1 Access to your personal data is only provided to our staff, business partners, suppliers and contractors. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, development of functionality for the Website, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.

5.2 By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

5.3 The security of your data is a matter of great importance to us. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

5.4 Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

5.5 We will be using a SSL connection on the Website when we collect your requests and billing information. But please remember, even if we use sophisticated encryption we cannot guarantee the security of the transmission of information over the internet. You should realise that such transmission is conducted at your own risk. However information will be kept on secure servers and key information encrypted if transmitted by us.

5.6 You provide your credit card or debit card details to our payment services provider who collects, processes and stores such data in accordance with its privacy policy. Although we do not store your credit card or debit card details, any such details that you provide may be accessed by and given to third parties, some of whom may be located outside the European Economic Area, who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy and for other purposes approved by you. Such parties may process and store such information, process credit card payments and provide support services on our behalf in respect of any orders placed by you on the Website.

###  **6\. OTHER WEBSITE LINKS**

6.1 We may include links as well as banner advertisements by clicking on which you will be redirected to other websites which may have different Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for, and have no control over those websites or their content. By using the Website you agree that we do not take on any liability that may arise from the use of any links that appears on the Website.

###  **7\. COOKIES**

7.1 Cookies are text files stored, either on a temporary or persistent basis on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies are used for authenticating, session tracking and maintaining specific information about the use and users of the Platform.

7.2 The data collected by cookies is anonymous. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer's hard drive by searching for files with "cookie" in it and deleting them. In addition, if you want to stop cookies from being stored on your computer, you can edit your browser settings so that cookies are blocked. Unfortunately, if you block cookies you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Platform. For more information about cookies, please visit: www.allaboutcookies.org

7.3 Web beacons consist of a small string of software code that represents a graphic image request on a page or email. There may or may not be a visible graphic image associated with the web beacon and often the image is designed to blend into the background of a page or email. Web beacons can be used for many purposes - including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, and personalization. Web beacons used by the Website collect only anonymous data.

7.4 The Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the Website and also allows us to improve the Website. By continuing to browse the Website, you are agreeing to our use of cookies for the following purposes:

When you use the Website, we may set and access cookies on your browser

(a) to remember your login or to keep session information;

(b) to make the website work more effectively; and

(c) anonymous cookies are used to analyse how many visitors come to the Website and to track how they use it.

7.5 You may refuse to accept cookies by adjusting your browser setting which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies or by clearing your cookies. However, if you do that, your use of the Website may be adversely affected.

7.6 On the Website, we are using information about your visit to serve you relevant advertisements on other websites, including Google, across the Internet. This is achieved by placing a cookie on your browser which is then called upon by a third-party website which then serves you our ad. Never in this process is personally identifiable information passed between us and the Website serving the ad.

7.7 You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager. Website may include links as well as banner advertisements of/to third parties which use information about your visits to this and other websites. The Website does not control the dissemination of their cookies. You should check relevant third party website for more information about this.

###  **8\. ACCESS AND UPDATE**

8.1 Users of the Website have the right to:

(a) Ask us for a copy of the information supplied by you that we hold by making request to [support@fabrily.com](mailto:support@fabrily.com). We are entitled to charge you a standard fee for this service but it would be unusual if we do so.

(b) Ask us to stop using your personal data or contacting you in the future with special offers or news of new services

8.2 The Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

###  **9\. OPT-OUT**

9.1 If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you. We will give you the option to opt out of our marketing communications or emails. If you would like to change these preferences then you should use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails or contact us.

9.2 Where we have disclosed your personal information to Campaign Creators pursuant to clause 4.3(d), such Campaign Creators are deemed to be authorized to send communications to you by electronic means and you hereby authorize them to do so. In the event that you do not wish to continue to receive emails from a Campaign Creator, you may opt out of their marketing communications and emails by clicking the unsubscribe link in any email from them.

###  **10\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

10.1 We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review and reserve the right to revise it at any time. It is your obligation to check the Website regularly to review our current Privacy Policy. You will be subject to the Privacy Policy in force at the time that you use the Website service.

###  **11\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO CAMPAIGN CREATORS**

11.1 In the event that we disclose personal information about any user of the Website to you as a Campaign Creator, you undertake and agree that you will only send that user relevant and targeted communications and emails and that you will not disclose such personal information to any other person without our prior written consent.

11.2 You further undertake that you will include an unsubscribe link in any email to any user and will ensure that the email address of any user who unsubscribes from your promotional emails is immediately removed from your database and is not sent further emails.

11.3 You undertake to comply in all material respects with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998.

11.4 You hereby indemnify us against any claim, loss or expense suffered by us by reason of any breach of the above by you and/or any failure to fully comply with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998 as amended from time to time.

###  **12\. COMPLAINTS OR QUERIES**

12.1 We intend to meet the highest standards when collecting and using your personal information. In any case you suspect that our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate we encourage you to bring it to our attention. We are happy to provide any additional information or explanation needed. no guarantee of the continued existence or availability of any options presented on the Website. By using the Website, you assume the risk that the information on the Website may be incomplete, inaccurate, out of date or may not meet your requirements. Any interpretation of the Website’s content, claims or disputes shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English Courts under English law.

12.2 Please, email us if you have any issues, comments or questions about the above on [support@fabrily.com](mailto:support@fabrily.com)
